CINDY PARK

UI UX DESIGNER / FRONT-END DEVELOPER

PROFILE

A certified front-end developer with 2 years of UI/UX design experience with a demonstrated history of working in the government services. Excellent in collaborating with other designers and developers to build creative and intuitive solutions for users while demonstrating stable leadership. A strong community and social services professional, proficient in both group and individual communication.

SKILLS

- Languages: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, React js
- Wireframing using Balsamiq, Figma, Adobe XD
- Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator
- MS Office Suite
- Fluent in Korean



CINDYPARK31@GMAIL.COM



WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/ CINDYPARK-PROFILE/

EDUCATION

DIPLOMA® BCIT® 2019-PRESENT

Studied Digital Design and Development with an outstanding GPA of 4.0. Polished a detailed web-based marketing plan for a local business using SEO strategies and tools to track the statistics. Project leader for 3 teams through a tight timeline of 8-9 course load.

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE • UBC • 2016-2018

Studied BSc in Biological Sciences for two years.

EXPERIENCE

GRAPHIC DESIGNER • CMU • 2018-2019

Designed and created required graphic assets to the Human Computer Interactions Institute (HCII) User-Based Lab at the Carneige-Mellon University.

LIFEGUARD/INSTRUCTOR • TOWNSHIP OF LANGLEY • AUG 2015-PRESENT

Coordinated with fellow lifeguards to maintain high level of safety of the facilities. Professionally led swimming lessons for various age groups of participants, from 6 months of age to seniors in their sixties.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE / LEADERSHIP

MARKETING DIRECTOR • AKCSE UBC • 2017-2019

Directed a team of 4 to create digital posters for educational events. Organized and designed an annual club hoodie sale.

HEAD DESIGNER • CKC 2018 • MAY 2018

Designed promotional products for 2018 Canada-Korea Conference on Science and Technology.